[Music]
case briefs and so much more LS status
got what you're looking for
in 2011 the Supreme Court of Texas heard
the case of Italian Cowboy Partners
limited V Prudential Insurance Company
of America a case focusing on a
landlord's duty to disclose material
information about a property to
commercial tenants restaurant owners
Jane and Francesco seki sought to open a
new location at Prudential Insurance
company's Dallas shopping center but
terminated the lease over a persistent
sewer gas odor they encountered during
the negotiations they then sued the
landlord and property manager for fraud
breach of the implied warranty of
suitability and recession of the lease
the court found that the contract's
unclear language did not waive the right
to sue for fraud and that the landlord
Prudential breached its obligation to
maintain the sewer system and the
implied warranty of suitability as well
as made misrepresentations during the
negotiations the Court held that the
lessee Italian cowboy was entitled to
lease decision and damages actual
damages were calculated by adding
investor contributions and interest debt
incurred and subtracting the remaining
assets value the Supreme Court of Texas
then reversed the court of appeals
judgment and remanded the case for
further consideration in favor of
Italian cowboy on its claim for
rescission due to prudential's breach of
the warranty of suitability
days briefs and so much more LS status
got what you're looking for
law elevate your mind leave the stress
of class
[Music]